Hello guys. Hello
guys, my name is uh.
My name is Mr. Da Least, I
am Arab, and today we're gonna be
reacting, uh, to Stefan's dum-bass
getting, uh, fired. He's gonna be idea
maker from now on. Uh, I am
uh. This guy is a.
Vector and Ali is gonna get hired
to be developerrr today. We're gonna see
Saudi office. Let's see, because I missed
the listing reacting.
Gracias sure I'm not being gracious to
you, mo(h)ter fuck-er.
What's wrong with you? You don't
have no skin, you send racist ni--er ni--er ni--er
in my server.
Oh my God, Sir, you're being lonely now.
This guy is so stupid. You see him. You
see him, guys? You see him?
You see that? Absolute ragebait. What?
"No, I'm not done with them."
OOH wait, tell me back. Wait, it doesn't
live Reaction. Oh my goddings, Wall/Ones.
Wait, this is so coolings. Oh my
God, I'm getting coolings. Huawei
and Woawoing and woawoing.
Let's see. "Not today, ste-fan. We
need to talk, There are reasons why he
said that"
I. Dude,
if you're going to be upfront running
everyone, you'll be the lonely biç
here. Said that or nothing.
Bro, you use one chord.
It's just not gonna sound. No proofing
proofing.
Uh.
That would be almost "He hates my
music taste." We all do bro. We
all do hate your music taste.
"Everyone has a taste."
"No like."
Wowing, wowing. This is so
cooling, reacting.
Wowing. Wowing, wowing, wowing. I show
you Mr. Beast. I saw you waiting.
Waiting. Waiting. Wait, Wait, wait, wait,
wait. Waiting. Waiting. Waiting. I'll
show you. What This Mr. Do you think?
Wait. I saw You want this Mr. Distinct.
Look, this is Mr. Least'ing.
Look. See. Guys, this is another
thing right there. See, this is Stefan.
See Stefan. Did you guys see
the phone? See, see,
see. This is Stefan. Wait, what the fuck?!
See, this is Stefan. (Ste is mr. least) Look, see,
here's Mr. V's son. Look, he's Mr. V
Sunny. He's Mr. V Sunny.
See, he's Mr. Least Thing.
Stephanie Stephanie Ling is a. (I give up editing subtitles here but im gonna be uncensoring words still -minusone_t)
Put me in Sammy office.
And bro hates me for listening to record
songs makes everyone hate me because I'm
listening to break or bro what me making
you hate you are spreading it.
You're telling me everything is bad? You
have a stupid mind. You tell me like
this, Stefan. And now you're saying like,
bro, he makes everyone hating me. Ling
Ling Brewing. What's wrong with you, Wing?
Oh my God thing, bro, Oh my God thing.
Just shut off Stefan. Why do you like
this? I'm about to be done with you. He
makes everyone hate me because I'm
listening to break on. What a lie, what a
lie. Stopping, stopping, what a lie. What
a lying. What lying? What lying. You're
lying, bro. Go to hell. Go to hell,
you're lying.
Yes, he protecting. He predicting. He
predicting. Particularly.
Look, See. See, see. I told you in
particular, I saw you. I told you. I told
you. I told you. I told you.
I get it, you all hate me. Is there
something to hide? I'm a bad person.
Early and yeah, yeah, yeah, you're
bad. You're bad. We we all
secretly hate you.
Sir,
Sir.
Uh.
If if you don't want to talk, talk with
him.
Oh, Oh yeah, Vector.
Oh my goodness. Oh my God. ING.
Why did you hit me?For listening to Break
our Music. Because
I think we really found out why. But
why you're you're Mr. Least? It's too
overrated, that's the reason. And what
the fuck is "Breaker Concert"?
Like nobody like that bro we love like we love
Bruno Mars, BBNO$. We love
Abhinav's concert. We love live events.
Not like this.
Totally. You weren't like this bro.
What about you? You were always hating on
us, now we secretly hate you back. Very
fair and squirting.
Growing.
I will be doing this at the same time by
the way. Yes admin abusing is in 15
minutes thing. If you want you can
joining. He successfully made me not able
to remove one of his brake or playlists.
Made one of his breakwording playlisting.
Because the word listening to record
before Ahmed disappearing because of you.
I might be in depression after this
message.
Please do not support him because he's
always accusing us #2.
I I made him good.
Do you know how many hate I got?
No matter what I do, not even caring.
OK bro, so happy. Oh şit my time is
nearly to the devil's hour. God, I have
back up.
Recording.
OK, correctly understanding started to
creating. Shout out to Vector-ine
Stephanie so useless.
I do have that game but I didn't play it
in two months. Uninstall. Uninstall
because repo is so bad. I mean it is good
but just keep it in case if I want to
play it with you.
I know Sammy. I'm about to finish with
this guy. Sammy, make the final thing and
then I'll fire the FAK out of him. I'm
about to give him the third warning.
Play by respect for that we gonna die.
Time of money. So believe I'm gonna be on
time. Just want to see how I warned him.
Yes yes, yes, yes, yes, of course.
Kebab. Kebab. Lebanese kebab. I'm
cooking. Watch. I'll watch you. Look,
look, look, look.
Watch me cook. Watch me cook.
No, but yeah, yeah, yeah. Yes, yes, yes,
yes. I know, I know, I know, I know.
Then we go to Alpha. And
you guys watch me cook his warning?
Boom, it's all awful.
Stephanie.
You guys, I'll send
you. I'll send you.
Guys, I got no warnings,
only Stephanie got warnings so
I show. Riding foes,
[MusicLyrics]: I'm poking, not on nice toes, drive slow,
my trunk up and the lights glow when I'm
sitting so low to the ground. I might
straighten fake Kenny the paint. I might
flake it riding down to 88 in the top
bake thinking you can run up on me. Then
you [Ahmad]: Guys look, look, look, look, look. I
show you. I show you, I'll show you.
[MusicLyrics2]: Everything flows from the grills to the
chain. I spent a lot of change. Now I'm
looking like. *unintelligible according to subtitles*
Kind of good dog.
[Ahmad]: I mean same messages before adding it.
Holy şitting, one more warning and he's
FOKING DONE HOLI SHITTINGS- HOLY SHİTTİNGS
Holy shit tings. Please put
background music here ✅✅✅ like very insane
background music like just edit this
video. Let's make this video popular on
YouTube. Let's see actually wait don't
upload it yet, but we'll upload it on
April 1, 2027 (we uploaded this at september 5 2026 instead of that date) and see how much views it
gets on you guys channels. (vectorbyte's channel)
We will see. And me,
my swing repose. A game on. Swearing is
not allowed. I'll let someone decide
that. OK. True. I'm sorry. Sorry. Stefan,
you are officially a member. Rules are
rules. I cannot go behind!!!!!!!!
[MusicLyricsFinal]: I can only mean one thing.